{
  "id": "french-numbers",
  "title": "French Numbers",
  "description": "French numbers from 1 - 10 with French on the front and English on the back.",
  "cards": [
    { "id": "n1", "front": "un", "back": "one" },
    { "id": "n2", "front": "deux", "back": "two" },
    { "id": "n3", "front": "trois", "back": "three" },
    { "id": "n4", "front": "quatre", "back": "four" },
    { "id": "n5", "front": "cinq", "back": "five" },
    { "id": "n6", "front": "six", "back": "six" },
    { "id": "n7", "front": "sept", "back": "seven" },
    { "id": "n8", "front": "huit", "back": "eight" },
    { "id": "n9", "front": "neuf", "back": "nine" },
    { "id": "n10", "front": "dix", "back": "ten" }
  ]
}

